<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English Learning on Walden</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/english-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English Learning on Walden</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:17:50 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/english-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Waves</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:17:50 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Waves are the children of the struggle between ocean and atmosphere, the ongoing signatures of infinity. Rays from the sun excite and energize the atmosphere of the earth, awakening it to flow, to movement, to rhythm, to life. The wind then speaks the message of the sun to the sea and the sea transmits it on through waves &amp;ndash; an ancient, exquisite, powerful message.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Past Life Of The Earth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:17:44 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is animals and plants which lived in or near water whose remains are most likely to be preserved, for one of the necessary conditions of preservation is quick burial, and it is only in the seas and rivers, and sometimes lakes, where mud and sit have been continuously deposited, that bodies and the can be rapidly covered over and preserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sporting Spirit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:17:34 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am always amazed when I hear people saying that sport creates goodwill between the nations, and that if only the common peoples of the would could meet one another at football or cricket, they would have no inclination to meet on the hattlefield. Even if one didn&amp;rsquo;t know from concrete examples (the 1936 Olympic Games, for instance) that international sporting contests lead to orgies of hatred, one could deduce if from general principles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Puma At Large</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:11:55 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/sample-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Pumas are large, cat-like animals which are found in America. When reports came into London Zoo that a wild puma had been spotted forty-five miles south of London, they were not taken seriously.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
