<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gastronomy on Explore Miño</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/categories/gastronomy/</link><description>Recent content in Gastronomy on Explore Miño</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>All rights reserved</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/categories/gastronomy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Galician cuisine</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/galician-cuisine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/galician-cuisine/</guid><description>&lt;p>Galicia is one of the regions with the richest gastronomy in Spain—and that’s no coincidence. Its Atlantic climate, the quality of its land and sea, and a strong culinary tradition have given rise to a unique pantry where authenticity, natural flavor, and respect for seasonal ingredients prevail. From the sea to the mountains, Galician food reflects a culture that celebrates good eating as part of its identity.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Restaurants</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/restaurants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/restaurants/</guid><description>&lt;p>Galicia is famous for its fresh produce, seafood, and traditional recipes, and in this area there are plenty of places to enjoy the best of Galician cuisine. Below are some recommendations so you don&amp;rsquo;t miss a bite.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Local markets</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/local-markets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/local-markets/</guid><description>&lt;p>Visiting the local markets of Miño and its surroundings is a way to connect with the essence of Galicia. Here, you don&amp;rsquo;t just buy fresh, seasonal products—you experience the daily rhythm of the locals, discover traditional recipes, and enjoy direct contact with producers. These are vibrant spaces full of color, flavor, and conversation, where the aromas of freshly baked bread, daily-caught fish, and just-picked fruit blend together.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>