<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Explore Miño</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Explore Miño</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>All rights reserved</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 23:59:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>¡Welcome to Miño!</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/welcome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 23:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/welcome/</guid><description>&lt;p>Discover this charming corner of Galicia, where the calm of the sea blends with the cultural and culinary richness of the region. We invite you to explore the surroundings and let yourself be surprised by the history, traditions, flavors, and local life of this welcoming coastal village. Start your journey here!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>History</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/history/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/history/</guid><description>&lt;p>The history of Galicia dates back to ancient times, over two thousand years ago, when its inhabitants built &lt;em>castros&lt;/em>—fortified hilltop villages—such as those of Baroña or Santa Tegra. These structures reveal an organized society, closely tied to the land and the natural environment. Celtic influences left a deep mark on Galician culture, visible in its music, symbols, rituals, and the way communities related to their landscape.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Galician cuisine</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/galician-cuisine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/galician-cuisine/</guid><description>&lt;p>Galicia is one of the regions with the richest gastronomy in Spain—and that’s no coincidence. Its Atlantic climate, the quality of its land and sea, and a strong culinary tradition have given rise to a unique pantry where authenticity, natural flavor, and respect for seasonal ingredients prevail. From the sea to the mountains, Galician food reflects a culture that celebrates good eating as part of its identity.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Nearby cities</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/nearby-cities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/nearby-cities/</guid><description>&lt;p>One of the great advantages of staying in Miño is its strategic location: within less than half an hour, you can visit charming towns, cities with centuries of history, and beautiful natural spaces. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a cultural excursion, a shopping day, or simply a stroll through streets full of Galician character, here are some of the best options.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Beaches</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/beaches/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/beaches/</guid><description>&lt;p>The beaches of Miño are undoubtedly one of its main attractions. Framed by the calm estuaries, Galician greenery, and a sun-friendly orientation, Miño becomes an ideal destination to enjoy the Galician summer without crowds or rush.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hiking</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/hiking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/hiking/</guid><description>&lt;p>Miño is an ideal destination for those who enjoy hiking. Its privileged location between sea and mountains allows you to discover a variety of landscapes, from peaceful beaches to lush forests, including historic routes like the Camino de Santiago.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Local festivities</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/local-festivities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/local-festivities/</guid><description>&lt;p>If you visit Miño during the summer months, you&amp;rsquo;ll find one of Galicia&amp;rsquo;s most deeply rooted and lively traditions: their local festivities. From mid-June to late September, each parish, town, or nearby village celebrates its festivity with a mix of religion, gastronomy, music, and vibrant street life. It&amp;rsquo;s the time of year when locals and visitors gather outdoors to share the best of Galician culture.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Restaurants</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/restaurants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/restaurants/</guid><description>&lt;p>Galicia is famous for its fresh produce, seafood, and traditional recipes, and in this area there are plenty of places to enjoy the best of Galician cuisine. Below are some recommendations so you don&amp;rsquo;t miss a bite.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Local markets</title><link>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/local-markets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venturarome.github.io/explore-mino/en/blog/local-markets/</guid><description>&lt;p>Visiting the local markets of Miño and its surroundings is a way to connect with the essence of Galicia. Here, you don&amp;rsquo;t just buy fresh, seasonal products—you experience the daily rhythm of the locals, discover traditional recipes, and enjoy direct contact with producers. These are vibrant spaces full of color, flavor, and conversation, where the aromas of freshly baked bread, daily-caught fish, and just-picked fruit blend together.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>